buzzhumor.com 2011-11-12

# Privacy Policy

 BuzzHumor is committed to respecting your online privacy and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. 

We have established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information. 

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. 

BuzzHumor strives to comply with all applicable laws that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, BuzzHumor intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this online Privacy Policy. 

It is against BuzzHumor's policy to sell Personal Information collected online. 

BuzzHumor intends to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. 

Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. Our tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times of activity. Our cookies and tracking technologies are used specifically for the purpose of BuzzHumor's operation and administration. Any information obtained through their use is protected from unauthorized access or disclosure. 

Third party Service providers are an important means by which BuzzHumor maintains its Web site. In some cases third party service providers may have access to secure data. BuzzHumor will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on our behalf. 

This site contains links to other sites. BuzzHumor is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

BuzzHumor.com extends the ability to our visitors to sign up and post content on our free public forums. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in the forums becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. These sites are responsible for their own privacy policies. 

Digital Millennium Copyright Act ("DMCA") Policy Introduction   
This policy is intended to implement the procedures set forth in 17 U.S.C. Section 512 and the Digital Millennium Copyright Act ("DMCA") for the reporting of alleged copyright infringement. It is the policy of Sparro's Web inc (the "Company") to respect the legitimate rights of copyright owners, their agents, and representatives. Users of any part of the Company computing system are required to respect the legal protections provided by applicable copyright law. 

Designated Agent   
The Company's Designated Agent to receive notification of alleged infringement under the DMCA is: Email: info at BuzzHumor.com 

Complaint Notice Procedures for Copyright Owners   
The following elements must be included in your copyright infringement claim:   
1 An electronic or physical signature of the copyright owner or a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed. 

2 Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notice, a representative list of such works at that site. 

3 Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit the Company to locate the material. 

4 Information reasonably sufficient to permit the Company to contact the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic mail address at which the complaining party may be contacted. 

5 A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law. 

6 A statement that the information in the notice is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed. 

Failure to include all of the above information may result in a delay of the processing or the DCMA notification. Notice and Takedown Procedure: It is expected that all users of any part of the Company system will comply with applicable copyright laws. However, if the Company receives proper notification of claimed copyright infringement it will respond expeditiously by removing, or disabling access to, the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity. Company will comply with the appropriate provisions of the DMCA in the event a counter notification is received.
